Obi-Wan Kenobi: A Jedi's Return is a documentary film directed by David Gelb.
This special explores the return of Obi-Wan Kenobi and Anakin Skywalker to the screen,
as well as Ewan McGregor and Hayden Christensen to their classic roles.
Director Deborah Chow leads the cast and crew as they create new heroes and villains that live alongside new
incarnations of beloved Star Wars characters, and an epic story that dramatically bridges the saga films.
Self - Obi-Wan Kenobi / Executive Producer, played by Ewan McGregor.
Self - Anakin Skywalker, played by Hayden Christensen.
Self - Director / Executive Producer, played by Deborah Chow.
Self - Reva Sevander, played by Moses Ingram.
Self - Leia Organa, played by Vivien Lyra Blair.
Self - Writer / Executive Producer, played by Joby Harold.
Obi-Wan Kenobi () is a fictional character in the Star Wars franchise.
In the original film trilogy, he is a Jedi Master who
trains Luke Skywalker in the ways of the Force.
In the prequel trilogy, he mentors Luke's father, Anakin Skywalker.
Obi-Wan is portrayed by Alec Guinness in the original trilogy
and by Ewan McGregor in the prequel films.
McGregor also plays the character in the
television series Obi-Wan Kenobi (2022).
Guinness's performance in Star Wars (1977) earned him the Saturn Award for Best Supporting
Actor, as well as a nomination for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor.
The film explores themes of behind the scenes, filmmaking, making of.
The tone is intense.